atlastechng.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Atlas Systems and Technology Solutions

The following policy dictates the manner in which Atlas Systems collects and uses information gathered from users of this (each, a "User").

## Privacy

Users' privacy is extremely important to Atlas Systems and we are committed to safeguarding the information you entrust to us. Atlas Systems will not disclose information about customers or users without express permission unless the release of said information is required by government subpoena.

## Information Collection Practices

Atlas Systems may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms and other instances where Users are invited to provide such information. Atlas Systems may also collect information about how Users interact with our website . This information is obtained through analysis of server logs and through the use of "cookies" placed on user machines. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on a PC to identify the User should they visit the website again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our website.

## Information Usage

Atlas Systems may use personally identifiable information collected through our website to contact Users regarding products and services offered by Atlas Systems and its trusted affiliates. Atlas Systems may also use information collected through our website for research regarding the effectiveness of the website and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of Atlas Systems, and its trusted affiliates.

## Information Disclosure

Atlas Systems will not disclose information about customers or users without express permission unless the release of said information is required by an Atlas Systems trusted affiliate to facilitate action requested by the client, or is required by government subpoena. However, we may transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of Atlas Systems' businesses.

## Questions

Please contact us with any questions regarding the Atlas Systems privacy policy by calling 08033683744 or email [support@atlastechng.com](mailto:support@hostmysite.com).
